特警屠龙
动作快一点
Faster!
拿一包给我
Give me a bag
大哥
Big Brother
正货，果然是实力派
The real thing, so it's lived up its name
海洛英，你要多少有多少
Heroine can be had in any quantity
听说你在纽约很吃得开，一起做过江龙
They say you've a way in NY. Let's combine
将美国的海洛英市场全部捉过来
to snatch your heroine businesses from them
好，有钱大家赚
Okay, it's mutually beneficial
现在我要二十公斤货
Now I want 20 kilos of that stuff
钱呢
Where's the money?
在这里
Here
别说我不把你教得聪明一点
Mind you
有一哥在这里，千万别乱说话
Don't talk nonsense in front of Mr. Big Brother
敢向我拔枪，你想找死？
Trying to draw? Are you looking for hell?
有种
Great!
我跟你合作，其他家族一定没生意可做
If you work with me, the other families will go bust
小熊是我的亲兄弟，拿二十公斤货来
He's my brother. Get 20 kgs of stuff for him
你这个死仔炳
You bustard Ping!
不许动，警察
Don't move, CID!
不许动
Don't move!
不许动，警察，把枪放下
Don't move! Police, drop your gun!
该死的
Damn it!
把枪放下
Drop your gun!
大哥，快跑
Big brother, run!
别动
Stay where you are!
把枪放下，慢慢起来
Drop your gun and climb up slowly
别想着耍花样，老子的枪很容易走火
No monkey business! My gun has no eyes
双手拉着自己的耳朵
Put your hands on your ears!
老子出马，从不失手
I never flop in any mission!
你妈的
Damn you!
你没事吧？德叔
Are you alright, Uncle Te?
没事
Yes
你怎么会老猫烧须？
Well, an experienced fireman gets his fingers hurt?
多事
Nonsense!
还想跑？
Trying to run?
走开
Get out of my way!
不要跑，警察
Stop, police
别动...
Freeze!
别乱来
Keep away!
快点把枪放下，还不放下我就打死她
Drop your gun! Drop or I'll kill her!
把枪放下，听到了没有？
Come on, put it down! Hear me?
否则我开枪打死她，快放下
Drop it or I'll shoot her dead
快放下
Drop it!
岂有此理，你这个死家伙
Outrageous! You scum
你这个家伙，想找死？
Are you sick of living?
全部蹲下
Keep down, police!
你这个家伙，不想活了？
Are you fed up with living?
追
After him!
莎莉，不要上来，危险
Shirley, don't come up! It's dangerous!
叫蛙人来打捞
Get the frogmen to salvage
是，长官
Yes, sir!
刚才你不要命了吗？
Did you mean to get killed?
对不起
Sorry!
黄长官
Mr.Huang
马上封锁现场，叫救伤车来
Cordon off the spot and call an ambulance
是，长官
Yes, sir!
黄长官...
Mr.Huang...
大家辛苦了
Thank you all for the trouble
差一点忘了哪里去找回一条鱼饵给莎莉
I nearly forgot to get back a bait for Shirley
德叔，看看找到了多少毒品
Uncle Te, see how much our haul is
是，长官
Yes, sir
修哥，你的眼镜修好了再还给你
Hsiu, here you are, fixed
好
Good
韦长官
Mr.Wei
美国有一个档案来了
Here's a file from the USA
这一班是美国新兴的贩毒集团
This new drug syndicate
现在来了香港
is now in HK
你留心一下他们的动静
Watch their movements
多喝一杯庆祝一下
Let's have more
已经喝了很多了
I've had enough
干杯...
Cheers!
不要... 什么不要
Don't... What?
我真的不能喝
Really can't drink
你骗人，不能喝
You're lying
好了...
Enough...
那我明天才多喝一杯
Well, I'll drink more tomorrow
明天再算
Let's talk about it tomorrow
事先声明
Listen
明天谁敢乱来就把他调到沙头角去
anyone making trouble tomorrow will be transferred to Shataukok
这不是公报私仇吗？
Are you trying to avenge a personal grudge
什么公报私仇？
What do you mean?
黄长官，你来评评道理
Mr.Huang judge for us
我们当他是朋友才替他庆祝一下
We celebrated for him because we took him for a friend
他现在不当我们是朋友，你有什么看法
He's not taking us for friends. What do you think?
你要帮帮我，要不然我醉定了
Help me, or I'll get drunk for sure
行
Okay
明天你结婚，如果你不跟我喝这一杯
You're getting married tomorrow. Drink this
莎莉就要替我收拾房子
or Shirley has to clean the house for me
对，莎莉要一个人留下来拾垃圾
Right, Shirley will stay to clear up the rubbish
你以为做家庭主妇那么容易
Don't think it's easy to be a housewife
那你想不想他喝，我是不大想
Do you want him to drink. I don't
怎么样？  喝了它
Well? Drink it
不要喝
Don't drink
喝这么大杯
Drink this big glass
你还没有过门就公然维护着他
Don't side with him so soon
看见你们俩这么恩爱
We bachelors...
真是令我们这一班王老五羡慕了
really envy your true feeling
你就开心了，明天就离开我们不干
You're Iucky, you're quitting tomorrow
不过手足们就真的不开心了
But we really are depressed
还搏什么？昨天医生才说过我的心脏不好
Why fight? Only yesterday the doctor said my heart's weak
什么？
What?
受不了刺激
I can't stand the shock
有时候医生的话用不着全相信的
Sometimes you can't take a doctor advice too serious
师姐，修哥受不了刺激，你受得
Sister, he can't stand the shock. Can you?
这一杯不喝也一样要留下来收拾房子
You don't drink this, you must clean the house
你去执骨好了
Go and collect the ashes
斗酒伤身不好的，不如斗气好吗？
Drinking's bad for health. What about venting our feeling?
更对胃口，我是处男
That suits me better. I'm a virgin
反正蹩了一肚子气，来，斗吧
I've lots of grievances, lets vent them
阿有，过来
Ah Yu, come here!
什么事，修哥？  你是怎么搞的？
What's it, Hsiu? What's wrong with you?
替我摆平他
Fix him for me
修哥，这个是命令还是私人感情？
Is that an order or a friendly request?
是自己人才叫你这么做
Only a friend would tell you to do this
是，长官
Yes, sir
这个游戏规则不准看，下颚不准动
No peeping and no moving of lowerjaws
鸡蛋吹到对方那一边就算赢
Anyone blowing the egg to an opponent win
准备
Ready?
开始
Start!
修哥，我帮你，你还耍我？
Hsiu, I'm on your side. Why tease me?
今天不玩就再没有机会玩了
Either we play today or never
玩？就算你是我师父，我也要耍你一次
Even if you were my master, I'd tease you
爱美...
Amy...
好厉害
Terrific!
整我？
Make fun of me?
不要玩了，爱美真的来了
Stop that. Amy really is coming
我才不管呢 真的来了
I don't care about her. She really is coming
来了又怎么样？
So what?
你不管我什么？
It's you who don't care about me
没什么
Everything alright?
爱美 什么？
Amy. What?
连我的女朋友你也敢耍
How dare you lay hands on my girl?
师姐保护我 不要玩了...
Protect me. Stop fooling around
算了吧
Forget it!
岂有此理
Outrageous!
去死吧
Bastard!
你这个死家伙，来真的
How dare you?
谁敢耍爱美我就要他好看
Anyone teasing Amy will get it
玩出火了...
He's flaring up
你怎么了？
What's the matter with you?
没事
It's alright
他们都是这么疯的，别理他们，烧东西吃
They're always so wild. Never mind them
黄长官，挡着他
Mr.Huang, stop him
你两个家伙又玩什么新花样？
What's you up to again?
这个臭小子打我
That bastard hit me
好心你们别玩得这么疯
Don't go so wild, will you?
报告黄长官，现在是观乐时光
Mr.Huang, now is the Happy Hour
就算是干妈下命令，我们也一于照玩
We'll go on even if Madam ordered us to stop
你两个马骝连我也敢耍
Dare you even to tease me?
对不起，长官
Sorry, sir
我们下水陪你
We'll go down to accompany you
来得好，敢把我扔下来
Good, you dared to fling me down
进来吧
Come in!
喝得我全身发烫
It really got into my head
给我弄杯咖啡解解酒
Get me a cup of coffee, will you?
麻烦你
Thank you
送给我的吗？
For me?
本来我是想拿来送给莎莉的
I planned to give it to Shirley
不过现在想起来还是你合用一点
Now I think it suits you better
那就要看看
It depends
这东西怎么会合我用？
How could it suit me?
今天晚上你就不合用
Not for tonight
不过从明天开始，就要疼爱莎莉
As of tomorrow, you need to love Shirley
做她的佣人
you're to work like a slave
上一次整我
You tease me last time
好，让我给你享用一点催泪气体
Well have some tear-gas
好让你结婚也哭个饱
So you'll cry on your wedding day
你不是这么夸张吧？
Don't exaggerate
我真是服了你
Okay, you win
让开
Make way
让我来
Let me
不用，笨手笨脚
No, you're cIumsy
那就最好了
So much the better
好，先享受一杯咖啡
Let me taste this nice cup of coffee
你心脏不好，以后不准喝咖啡
Your heart's weak. Don't drink coffee anymore
怎么你当真的？我是骗他们的
I only meant to fool them
那你连我也骗了？
You've fooled me too
不是...
No
不准骗，快点老老实实说
Stop lying, tell me the truth
你是不是喜欢莎莉？
Do you love Shirley?
不肯说就是不喜欢了
If you don't say it, it means you don't
不是，不过...
No, but...
不过想了这么久就是还没有决定
I still can't make up my mind after such a long time
那我喜欢好了
I love her then
说得这么随便，就是没有诚意
You're not sincere
讲完了没有？
Have you finished talking?
催你了，走吧
Go now, They're pushing
那我走了
I'll go then
拜拜...
Bye-bye!
真没心肝，笨蛋...
Really heartless, idiot
先脱了它
Take it off first
是
Right
记着明天早上十点我来接新娘
Remember to collect the bride at 10 tomorrow
结一条领带
Wear a necktie
谢谢，拜拜
Thank you. Bye-bye
快点来试一试
Try it at once
真漂亮
Really beautiful
头花很好看
The flower on the head is beautiful
修哥
Hsiu!
别跑
Don't run
修哥
Hsiu!
快点叫救伤车
Call an ambulance at once!
修哥
Hsiu...
莎...莎莉，我...
Shir..Shirley, I...
修哥...
Hsiu...
发生什么事？
What happened...
警察
C.I.D
全人类的天父
Heavenly Father of all men
我们特为所爱而以后不能再见的人
We pray especially for those we love
向主祷告
but can't see any more
求主赐平安予他们，以永恒之光照临他们
May you bless them and shine on them
在主的慈爱、智慧及全能权柄当中
May the love, wisdom
愿天父的完全旨意
and omnipotence
所有的良善目的能在他们身上献上
be demonstrated in them
此乃我主耶稣基督要求，阿门
We pray in Jesus' name, Amen
你正在休假，你干么还回来？
Why are you back from your leave?
现在休假也没意义
There's no point in taking leave now
米高，我想申请销假
Michael, I'm applying for return to duty
也好，有事情做对你会好一点
Good. Work may do you good
八爷，我真的有麻烦，你要帮我一下
Master. I'm in trouble. You must help
你这个家伙，搞到这么严重
You made things so bad
手足们怎么肯帮你
Who'd help you?
这样吧，这里有一服花旗参
Here's a potion of American ginseng
看它能不能够帮到你
See if it will help
不要动，警察
Don't move. Police
阿有，把他铐上
Yu, handcuff him
不要动
Don't move!
潮洲雄在什么地方？
Where's Swatow Hsiung?
不知道，大姐
I don't know. Miss
不知道...
I don't know...
说
Speak up!
我真的不知道
I really don't know
你跟他是好兄弟，怎么会不知道？讲
You're his best friend! Speak up!
讲
Speak up!
我看你讲不讲
Are you going to speak or not?
长官，他不肯讲，说不定这两个怪兽会讲
Maybe these 2 monsters may speak
不要，我什么都不知道
Sorry, I don't know anything
走
Let's go
不要，老大
Don't, Mr.Big
到那边去
Go over there!
不要吓倒我的女上司
Don't scare madam
你们两个聪明的就快点讲
Be smart and speak
我真的不知道
I really don't know
如果不肯讲的话，烫焦了屁股我可不负责
Don't blame me if your bottom gets burnt
听到了没有？
Hear that?
我真的不知道
I really don't know
怎么了？不讲是吗？讲
Well, are you going to speak or not. Speak up!
脱裤子
Take off your pants!
不讲是吗？烫他
You're not speaking? Scald him
好了
Good
我最喜欢烫屁股
I enjoy doing it
岂有此理，敢不把老子放在眼内
You don't care a damn about me
还不快讲？讲不讲？
Speak up!
还不讲...
No?
昏过了去了
He's collapsed
当然了，屁股给烫焦了
His bottom's got burnt
外面那一个可能熬得住
That one outside may last longer
好，烫他 拿来
Okay, scald him. Give it to me
脱裤子
Take off your pants
我讲...我只知道他明天坐船逃亡
I'll speak... I only know he's sailing tomorrow
在什么地方我就不知道，我就知道这么多
but I don't know where
不要过来...
Keep away...
看看我们收到多少投诉
Look, we've got so many complaint
未经批准，就擅自行动
You took action without my approval
滥用暴力，伤害疑犯，叫我怎么保住你？
used violence to hurt suspects. How can I protect you
何雪玲督察，你这一次令我太失望了
Inspector Ho Hsueh-ling, you've let me down
对不起，长官
Sorry, sir
现在说对不起...有什么用？
What good to say sorry now?
你当了警察这么久
How long have you been in the police force?
以你跟阿修的关系
With your relationship with Hsiu
根本就不应该办这件案
you shouldn't handle this case
我跟阿修还没有正式结婚
We're legally...
法律上不算是夫妻
still unmarried
住口
Shut up!
讲法律？我们当警察随时随地都可能殉职
To talk about law, we'll all die martrs
如果每一个人都要报仇
Vengeance makes us
跟流氓有什么分别？
no different from rascal
你没有资格当警察
You're unfit to be a policeman
对不起，长官
Sorry, sir
何雪玲督察这一次行动是经过我口头批准
Insp Ho's operation got my verbal approval
整件事情我最清楚
I know the whole thing well
你不用维护她
Don't cover her up
我只是觉得我需要负责
I only feel that I've a responsibility
好，你这么喜欢负责，你搞定它
Good fix it then
再有什么差错，小心你自己的前途
If anything goes wrong again, mind your future
是，长官
Yes, sir
我替你背这个黑锅也没所谓
I don't mind bearing the blame for you
可是有时候办案不是靠冲动就行
But remember foolhardiness doesn't always work
黄长官 德叔，怎么样？
Mr. Huang! Uncle Te, how's it?
有线索
We've a gIue
潮洲雄会在两点钟
Swatow Hsiung will leave HK
会在三门仔码头坐船离开香港
at Sam Mun Pier at two
老兄，还有多久才开船？
Buddy, when will the ship sail?
搬完这几桶就行了
After these drums have been moved
潮洲雄
Swatow Hsiung
不许动，快开船
Don't move! Sail quickly!
开船，否则一枪打死你
Sail, or I'll shoot you dead
解缆
Release the rope
老大，你不要开枪，全船都是汽油
Brother, don't shoot, it's loaded with gasoline
我一家大小全在船上
My whole family's on it
求求你，你千万不要开枪
Don't shoot. I beg you
解缆，快一点
Release the rope, faster!
去死吧
Go to hell!
不要动
Don't move!
你这么做会犯法
You're violating the law
泰利叫船家开船驶回岸去
Terry, tell the bastard to bring the boat back to shore
阿有，把现场的证物全收拾好带回去
Yu, keep the evidence on the spot and bring it back
知道了黄长官
Yes, Mr.Huang
船主，把牌照和身份证拿出来
Captain, show me your license and I.D
长官，不关我的事
Not my fault, sir
没事了，先驶回岸去
Back to the shore
上了岸再替你落口供
We'll take your statement then
我也很想杀他
I wanted to kill him too
别再说了
No more
但是我们是警察
We're police
干什么？
What are you doing?
老鬼德，花旗参那一件事我知道的
OId Te. I know the American ginseng case
放我一条生路，大家都好
Give me a chance. It's for everyone's good
你的废话真多，拜山时再说
Save your nonsense for the Tomb Festival
黄长官...
Mr.Huang...
把这些全部搞定
Fix all these
黄长官，你知不知道花旗参的事？
Mr.Huang, do you know the American ginseng case?
黄长官
Mr.Huang
聪明的你就放我一马，否则大家同归于尽
Be smart and let me go or we'll both penrish
开枪打死我好了
Kill me!
我看你怎么写报告，开枪吧
See how you'll make your report
你走
Get away...
抢枪... 不要动
A snatcher... Don't move!
过去看看他
Go and see him
过来这边，你留在这里看着他
Over here, you stay to watch him
是，长官
Yes, Madam
你过来，过来这边划位
Come here! Come here to mark the seat
不要让其他人走过来
Stop the others from coming
老鬼德，你是不是给吓坏了
OId Te, were you scared?
这柄枪要拿回来做证物
You need this gun for evidence
是...忘记了
Oh. I forgot
吓呆了
He was stunned
这些咖啡是一个巴西朋友送给我，试一下
This coffee came from my friend in Brazil. Try it
谢谢长官
Thank you, sir
我看过昨天那一件事的报告
I've read the report on yesterday's incidence
韦长官
Mr.Wei
这一件案虽然拿不到满分
We got no fulI marks
但是我已经很满意
but I'm satisfied with the result
可惜留不到活口，不然可以问多一点线索
Had we captured on alive, we could get more cIues
我就是喜欢你这点，对自己要求这么严格
I like you for your serious attitude
你已经够忙了，放两天假休息一下
You're already so busy. Take 2 days' leave
谢谢长官
Thank you, sir
有鱼上钓了，我钓到它了
A fish has swallowed the bait
你过来看看
Go and see
好大条
A big fish
你也会钓到鱼，鱼之中这一条算笨了
Even you've caught it, must be a stupid fish
不知道是你笨还是它笨？
So you're stupider!
那样也可以 它快要掉下去
Is that possible? It's going to drop down
快点捉着它 小心点...
Catch it at once. Be careful...
看错了，原来鱼也是这么古惑
I've seen it. So it's a crafty fish
是
Is it?
海里都是笨鱼，再钓别一条好了
There's no lack of stupid fish. Let's catch
我跟你出来玩也希望你能开心点
I daren't convey anything to you
干么还那么闷
but you can trust me
我教你驾帆船，以后跟你一起横渡太平洋
Let's me teach you yatching. Some day we'll cross the Pacific
来...
Come!
不行...
No...
转...
Turn...
转哪一个方向？
Which way
转这一边吗？
This away?
对了，转...
Right. Turn
是不是这样转...？
This way?
继续...
Go on
我行了
I did it
德叔
Uncle Te
阿有，有空要多点陪伴爱美
Yu, spend more time on Amy
不然很容易分手
to strengthen the ties
我也想
I wish I could
谁叫我当警察？
But I'm a policeman
我先走了
Excuse me
好，拜拜
Okay! Bye-bye
我是阿有
This is Yu
什么事？
What happened?
黄长官
Mr.Huang
我亲眼看到德叔跟几个洋鬼子买卖毒物
I've caught Uncle Te dealing drug with foreigner
没有可能
Impossible
是真的，我拍了录影带做证
It's true. I've the video tape for evidence
我不如马上采取行动？你认为怎么样
Let's make immediate action. What do you suggest?
不要，这一件事可能牵涉很大
No, it could be complicated
你明天把录影带回警察局给我看看
Bring all the tapes to the station for me to see
有急事？
Anything important?
小事情，我先送你回去
Nothing serious. I'll take you home
走吧
Let's go
仙蒂姐叫我提醒你，今天是爱美的生日
Cindy wants me to remind you today is Amy birthday
我知道了，我当然知道了
I know. I know
蛋糕和花都帮你买好，去逗她求她原谅你
See the cake and flowers is ready. Go and be pardon
还想什么？快上车
What are you waiting for! Get in!
女人，你不求不拜很容易拜拜...
Girls have to be soothed
知道了，三八
I know, you nosey
快点去，爱美快要下班了，走吧
Go now. Amy will be off duty soon
你真多事
You're meddlesome
泡妞只准十五分钟
Only 15 minutes for fooling around
头等机票两张 谢谢
Two first class airtickets. Thank you
谢谢你
Thank you
爱美
Amy
先生，买机票吗？
Can I help you, sir?
是，我想买两张机票跟我的女朋友去旅行
Yes. I want 2 tickets for a trip with my girlfriend
因为是她的生日，祝你生日快乐
It's her birthday. Happy birthday!
送给你的
It's yours
拍了些什么？让我先看看
What's it on the tape? Let me show it
回去煮些什么给我吃？
What are you going to cook for me?
吃完饭再吃蛋糕
Let's eat cakes after dinner
你干么看我的录影带？开门
Don't touch my videotape recorder! Open the door
开门 干什么？
Open up! What are you doing?
不关你的事
It's none of your business
出来...
Come out...
谁叫你看我的录影带？
Who told you to watch my videotape
好，连这么严重的事也不告诉我？
Well, you're keeping such a serious thing from me
什么事？
What is it?
你有没有把我当做兄弟？
Are you taking me for your brother
你说...
Speak up...
你真笨，德叔是你师父
Uncle Te's your master
他有没有告诉你他贩买海洛英
but he's keeping it from you
哪就是不相信我，是不是？
It means he doesn't trust me
很难说，你把德叔看成是你老爸
Who knows? You're taking him for you dad
我怎么知道你有没有份
How do I know you're an accessory?
这一种勾当，会说我有份
Would I be an accessory to this?
我跟你一起出生入死这么久
I went through everything with you
你这样也怀疑我？
and you suspect me?
你...你这么冲动，我怎么可以告诉你？
You're so impulsive. How could I tell you?
告诉你岂不是害了你？
It would only ruin you
你现在怕什么，怕什么？
What have you to fear now?
我也不怕，你怕什么？管他是老虎
I'm not afraid either. Be he a tiger
就算是我的亲生爸爸
or my own dad
他贩买海洛英我一样要捉他，你知不知？
I'll take him if he sells drug
我马上就去捉他
I'll go and arrest him right now
放手
Let's go!
你别这么冲动好不好
Don't be so impulsive!
你再这么冲动就什么都被你破坏了
Any rash action will ruin everything
我们是不是兄弟？
Aren't we brothers?
我现在告诉你，这事只有我跟黄长官知道
Listen this is only between me and Mr.Huang
还有我
And me
对了...
Yes...!
记着，有什么发现，不要私自行动，OK？
Remember, don't take individual action if you discover anything. Okay?
糟了，我要找爱美解释
Bad. I must explain to Amy
别乱来
Don't do anything foolish!
你听我说
Listen
好痛
It hurts!
你再不走我就报警，说有个警察擅闯民居
Go now, or I'll call the police and accuse you of trespassing
你不是这样开玩笑吧？
You must be joking
谁跟你开玩笑，跟你的朋友玩好了
Who's joking with you?
爱美
Amy
不想看到你，走
I won't see you anymore. Go away!
我的手
My hand!
你赖死不走是吗？我走
You're not going? I will
干什么？
What are you doing?
不许动
Don't go
你当我是犯人？
Are you taking me for a criminal?
是，我控告你蓄意伤害警务人员自尊心
Yes. I sue you for willful damage to a policeman's pride
我现在盘问你
I must question you now
我追了你十多条街，说了几十句对不起
I've followed you all the way and kept saying 'sorry'
你还想我怎么样？
What else do you want?
方长官，我想你尊重一下我
Mr.Fan, I want you to have some respect for me
你心情好的时候就来找我
You come to see me when you're in the mood
你心情不好的时候就扔下我
You leave me behind and say sorry
说声对不起就算数
when you're not
你把我看成是什么人？
What are you taking me for?
当你是我的女朋友，值得我对你说对不起
My girlfriend, worthy of my respect
值得我用行动来表示对我有多重要
Have my action to show how important you're to me
我现在开始陪你到明天早上
I'll keep you company till tomorrow morning
警察也不做，够了没有？
I'll quit as a policeman. Okay?
不够
No
市民也不做，街也不去，连传呼机也不要
I'll give you as a citizen to go out
跟所有人绝交，我绝不放你
I'll break with anyone else, but I won't let you go
你快点放了我
Let me go!
不放，今天晚上一于重色轻友
No, you mean everything to me
你不放手我怎么煮饭？死相
I can't cook if you don't let me go, jerk
是，你说得对，让我放了你
Right, right, I must let you go
等我先看看你有没有受伤
Let me see if you're hurt
警察非礼，罪加一等
A policeman gets more sentence for indecent assault
撤职也值得
I couldn't care less
信有，你搞什么鬼？进来帮帮我
Yu, what are you up to? Come and help
我在给你弄一份生日礼物
I'm preparing a birthday gift for you
来吃东西
Come and eat
大礼物来了
The big gift is here
我可不可爱
Am I sweet?
整个人送给你
Take me
真核突...
Disgusting...
莎莉，有没有锁匙？
Shirley, have you got the key?
以前就没有
Yes
这一个柜阿修一直都不让我打开
but Hsiu never allowed me to open it
我也不知道有什么放在里面
and I don't know what it contains
你送给他的？
Did you give him this?
他什么事都放在心里，从来不跟我说
He always kept everything to himself
一千多万
Over $10 million!
以他的家当和收入，没有可能有这么多钱
Impossible for a man of his family background!
还有两个护照，要来什么用？
And these 2 passports! What are they for?
这些钱是用不正当手段赚回来的
This must be ill-gotten money
这两个护照是预备在被人揭发的时候...
These passports are to help use another identity
随时可以用另一个身份离开香港
to get out of HK, in case of need
希望我的想法是错的
Wish my reasoning was wrong
最近我接到线报
I've recently got a tip-off that
说我们的部门有人利用职权贩卖海洛英
someone abused his power for dope-push
我一直以为他很忠直，原来什么都是假的
I thought he was honest
莎莉，我很明白你的心情
Shirley, I know how you feel
希望你可以面对现实
Please face up to reality
阿修的确有可疑，不过你放心
There's indeed something wrong with him
我一定帮你，一定帮你查出真相
but I'll help you find out the truth
先生，买支旗...
Buy a flag, sir...
跟着前面的白色车
Follow that white car in front
皇家警察，你不想着警察局的事吗？
Royal HK policeman, no more police affair
我才不理它的死活
No
今天晚上我整个人都属于你
I'm all yours tonight
滚开
GET LOST
警察
Police
把枪放下
Drop your gun!
老鬼德，把你的枪也扔掉
Drop your gun too, old Te
泰利，我...
Terry, I...
留下来跟法官说，把枪扔到海里去
Stay to speak to the judge. Filing it to see
拿你的手铐把两个洋鬼子铐上
Get you handcuffs and put them on
把他们铐上
those two foreigners
泰利
Terry
你贩毒？
You're trafficking in drugs
你身为警务人员，竟然知法犯法
As a policeman, you know the law and violate it
我年轻的时候也跟你一样这么大火气
I was as hot-tempered when I was young
我明白
I understood
我不明白你为什么要这样做？
Why did you do that?
我从学堂出来就一直跟着你
I've followed you since I left school
我当你是我师父，当你是我的爸爸
I took you for my master, my dad
但是今天我跟你的关系到此为止
but now it's all over between us
我要拉你
You're under arrest
拉我？当年我比你还勇
Arrest me? I was braver than you
为了拉几个小卒，你看我得到些什么？
What did I get for arresting some small frys
两个破奖章
2 lousy medals
翻风落雨就痛得我一整个晚上都睡不着
When the weather's bad, it hurts and I can't sleep
他们坐完牢出来，不也是一样贩毒
They did it again once they got discharged
我也是个小卒
I am a small fry too
我不理是小卒还是大魔头
A small fry or a big shot
总之栽在我手里一样没情讲
I don't care
泰利，你还年轻，你有理想是对的
Terry, you're still young and you're your idea
但是当你好像我家里的环境，这么需要钱
When you reach my age and are
我什么也不懂，什么也没有
in my straitened circumstances
你就会知道钱是那么重要
You'll see how important money is
你住口，你不用找借口原谅自己
Shut up! Don't find an excuse for yourself
泰利，放阿叔一马
Terry, let me go
我不可以放你，德叔
Sorry, Uncle Te
我知道你对我好，我也不想
I know you're nice to me, but I've no choice
黄长官，我在赤柱圣士提反湾
I caught Te dealing in drugs
捉到德叔跟两个洋鬼子交易
with 2 foreigners in Stephen Bay, Stanley
来...
Come on
停手...
Stop...!
小子，你们动就会死
Don't move, or you'll die
黄长官
Sir
就是这两个洋鬼子跟德叔交易毒品
these 2 foreigners dealt in drugs with Uncle Te
我已经拍了录影带做证据
I've got the tape for evidence
好，你做得很好，立了大功
Well done! You're done a great credit
把德叔铐起来
Handcuff Uncle Te
是，长官
Yes, sir
你们走吧，我跟你的波士解决一切
I'll fix everything with your boss. Leave now
好的
Okay!
你干么要杀死他？
Why do you want to kill him?
他不死你就死定了
You'll die for sure if he doesn't
我宁愿坐牢...
I'd rather go to jail...
也不愿杀死他
than to kill him
你是我至好的手下，我一定会罩着你的
You're my best aide. I'll cover you up
我不干了
I quit
替我办完了这件案再说
Finish this case for me first
这里的事你知道怎么处理，就这么决定
You know how to handle the things here
你曾经向我亲口保证过
You gave personal assurance that
说这一次的合作一定不会出事
everything would be okay
我保证的是那些货，没有说过当你的保母
Only about the stuff. I'm not your nanny
我真是高估了你的实力
I've overassessed you
连一个小子也搞不定
You can't even finish a kid
我跟你的合作到此为至
Now the co-operation is over between us
我们纽约的市场那么大
Our market in New York is so big
香港这边有很多人争着做我的拍档
Many in HK would vie to be my sidekick
OK，没问题
Okay, no problem
不过我告诉你
Listen
凡是我碰过的生意没有人敢再碰
no one dare touch any deals I touched
香港是我的，美国市场不单止你们
Hong Kong is mine, and you're not the only market in USA
马上离开香港回纽约去
Get out of HK and return to New York
慢着，米高
Hold it, Michael!
我来这里是赚钱，不是找仇人
I came here to make money, not to make enemy
好，我再相信你一次
Okay, I'll trust you one more time
好，如果要合作就帮我做一点事
Well, if you want co-operation, do one thing for me
明天晚上我要二百斤货
I want 200 kilos of stuff tomorrow night
这一个是我的户口号码
This is my A/C No.
明天早上你存了钱，晚上可以收到货
Credit the money into it. You'll g et the stuff tomorrow night
这个凶手一定跑不掉
The killer can never get away
手足们一定可以捉到他
We can get hold of him for sure
早安
Morning!
干么你们每一个人都苦口苦脸
What's wrong? Why are you all wearing a stone face?
死了老爸是不是？
A bereavement?
阿有 阿有，进来
Ah Yu. Ah Yu, come in!
莎莉，请你先出去一会
Shirley, please go out for a while
阿有，关门，谢谢
Ah Yu, close the door please
我查到阿修贩毒
I've ascertained Hsiu's drug-trafficking
真的？莎莉知不知道？
Is that so? Does Shirley know it?
我不敢肯定
I'm not too sure
会不会她也有份？
Would she be an accessory?
我想我们以后都要小心点
We must take more care from now on
我真不敢相信莎莉都有份
I don't think Shirley has a hand on it
这一盒是德叔跟毒贩交易的录影带
Here's a cassette of Te's drug-trafficking
我想这一件事，事关重大
It's of serious consequence
之前有阿修，现在是德叔
Formerly it was Hsiu, now it's Uncle Te
究竟还有多少人牵涉在里面，我也不知道
How many more are involved I don't know
阿有，你还有没有其他证据
Yu, have you got any other evidence?
我过了一盒带子放在爱美家里
I've put a tape at Amy's
是吗？
Is that so?
不用怕
Don't worry
爱美也不知道我放了一盒带了在她家里
Amy knows nothing about it
我们要尽快把那盒带子拿回来
We must get it back as soon as possible
为了爱美的安全，你不要再对任何人说
For Amy's safety, don't tell anyone about it
我知道该怎么做了
I know what to do
莎莉，请你进来
Shirley, please come in
阿有，有一件事要跟你说
Yu, I want to talk to you
你不要冲动，你要冷静一点
Keep cool
昨天晚上发生了一件事
Something happened last night
什么事？
What is it?
进来
Come in
黄长官
Mr.Huang
莎莉，这是重要证物，替我放在保险箱里
Shirley, put this important item in a safe
你不怕她是德叔的同党
Aren't you afraid she might be Te's accompany
不会吧
Impossible
昨天泰利被人杀死了
Terry was killed yesterday
什么？
What?
他知道老鬼德的事，这就...
He knew about OId Te
我出去一会
I must go out for a while
不要走，老鬼德，你这个死家伙
OId Te, hold it! You creep!
你害死了泰利，我打死你
You ruined Terry. I'll kill you!
阿有
Ah Yu
你疯，德叔当泰利是自己的孩子，你误会
Are you crazy? Uncle Te's taking Terry for his own son. You're mistaken
阿有，你别胡思乱想，他怎么会这样做？
Yu, don't get the wrong idea. He won't do that
你疯了？
Are you crazy
停手
Stop!
发生什么事？
What happened?
他当警察也贩毒，有什么事干不出？
A policeman trafficking in drugs can do anything
别吵，大家自己兄弟，有话好说
Quiet! We're all friends. Let's talk it over
放开我
Let me go!
我有证据证明你贩毒
I've proof of your drug-trafficking
我已经报告黄长官，我一定指证你
I've already reported to Mr.Huang. I'll testify against you
阿有，不要这么冲动
Yu, don't be impulsive
你是曾向我报告，但我没有看到证据之前
You did report to me, but I can't accuse Te
不可以一口说定是德叔
before I see the evidence
不用看了，一定是他
It must be him
我有你跟贩毒交易的录影带
I've got tapes of your drug-trafficking
你胡说
Nonsense
莎莉，放给他看
Shirley, run it for him
放给他看
Run it for him
你还是这样...
Don't ...
放吧
Run it
怎么没有？
How come?
原来是有的，我的录影带被人换了
Obviously the cassette has been swapped
换什么，证据呢？
What? Where's the evidence?
作贼心虚，我说你才有嫌疑
You yourself are under suspicion
你自己作贼心虚
You're exposing your own crime
上一次修哥之死
Last time Hsiu got killed
是因为你在他的车上装了烟幕弹
because you planted a smoke bomb
这一次泰利的死是因为你擅离职守
This time Terry got killed because you abandoned your duty
你有什么解释？
What explanation can you give?
守他的贮物柜
Search his locker!
我亲眼看见他把海洛英放在里面，开...
I saw him putting heroin in...
我也看见你把海洛英放在贮物柜里面
I also saw you put heroin into the locker
要搜就大家一起搜
Let's search together
我怕你吗？你死定了，把锁匙拿来
I'm not afraid. You're finished. Give me the key
别乱来
Don't try anything foolish
走开
Keep away!
德叔，把锁匙拿出来
Uncle Te, the key!
山鸡
Pheasant
不好意思，德叔
Sorry, Uncle Te
冷静
Keep cool
不要乱来
Don't mess around
德叔，真的是你
Uncle Te, you really did it
你收起了我的书还说不见了
You put aside my book and said it was missing
你搜清楚一点行不行？
Will you search more thoroughly?
全部搜过了，什么都没有
We've searched everything. There's nothing
搜他的家，一定有的
Let's search his home
阿有，那你的贮物柜...
Ah Yu, your locker...
打开来看看
Open it and see
好了
Okay
搜吧
Search!
真是你的 不是我的
You really did it. No
冷静一点...
Yu, calm down
你不是想告诉我这一包是面粉吧？
Are you going to tell me this is flour?
这东西不是我的，你嫁祸给我
This bag is not mine
冷静一点
Calm down
你相信我，莎莉，相信我
Believe me, Shirley, believe me
现在我什么人也不会再相信
Now I won't trust anyone
只会相信事实，相信证据
I only believe in truth and evidence
我现在用藏毒的罪名拘捕你
You're arrested for drug possession
莎莉，我知道陷害我的不只德叔一个
Shirley, I know Te is not alone in the frame-up
那一班人我早晚会找出来，你小心一点
Soon I'll seek them out! Watch out
你这不是说我们吗？你冤枉好人
Do you mean us? Don't frame us
你自己不好就算了，别把大家都拖...
Don't get us involved because you're evil
别吵，这里是街市？
Quiet, this is not a market
你们是纪律部队
You're the Discipline Unit
阿有跟德叔互相指控，我会撤查
I'll investigate the accusation between Yu and Uncle Te
你们也是一样，要接受内部调查
You'll also be subject to internal investigation
我是毒品调查科特别行动组督察何雪玲
I'm drug Investigation Special Operation Insp Ho
我怀疑你藏毒，叫什么名字
You're suspected of drug possession. What's your name?
方信有
Fan Shun-yu
职业
Occupation
香港皇家警察队雇员
A member of the Royal Hong Kong Police Force
隶属毒品调查科特别行动组
with the Drug Investigation Dept of the Special Operations
住在哪里？
Where do you live?
明知故问
You know it already
你曾经是警察，你应该知道...
As a policeman, you should know...
这一点我比你更清楚
I know better in this respect
我在你的贮物柜找到海洛英，你怎么解释
I've discovered heroin in your locker, how do you explain that?
怎么解释？我是被人插赃嫁祸的
I was framed. Why should I explain?
我没有藏毒，我不用接受你的盘问
Possess no drugs, why should I be question
没有一样证据支持我可以相信你的话
There's no evidence to support your state
那就是你有证据可以指证我了
You mean you've proof against me?
你想清楚有什么可以证明你是无辜的
Can you think of anything to prove your innocence?
法律是要讲证据的
Law requires evidence
你所说的一切都会作为是呈堂证供
All your statement may be used as evidence in court
好，我说
Okay, I'll give my statement
我藏毒、贩毒、走私
I deal in drugs, smuggling and
杀人放火、打劫
resort to killing, arson and robbery
你写好了，例行手续，你写吧
Take it down as a matter of routine! Come on
呈堂证供是吗？写吧
Evidence in Court? Take it down!
阿有
Ah Yu
我的名字叫方信有，我不认识你
My name is Fan Shun-yu, I don't know you
我怀疑督察何雪玲串谋害我，写吧
I suspect Insp Ho Hsueh-ling's conspiracy against me
写...告我好了
Take it down! Sue me
现在是八八年十月二十日下午三点
The time is 20th Oct 1988 at 3 p.m
我是扫毒组探员方信有，探员编号3368
I'm Anti-Narcotics Bureau detective Fan Shun-yu No. 3368
我怀疑同组警长冯建德贩毒
I suspect my Sergeant Feng Chien-te of drug-trafficking
经过三天的调查和跟踪
As a result of 3 days probe and trace
现在发现他在渡海轮上
I've discovered him dealing in drugs with...
跟两个身份未明的外籍人士进行毒品交易
2 unidentified foreigners on a ferry
据我暂时的推测
deduced that he used his detective identity
他利用扫毒组探员身份掩饰进行毒品交易
to cover up his trafficking activities
黄长官？
Mr.Huang
Mr.Huang?
老鬼德，我把全个房子都搜过了
I'm OId Te, I've searched the whole house
录影带有很多盒
There are many cassettes
不过没有看到你所说的那一盒
but not the one you mention
我先回来再说
Come back before we take any action
有没有线索？
Any cIues?
你先回去休息，这里由我来处理
Go back and take a rest. I'll take charge here
黄长官
Mr.Huang
阿有，我相信你是无辜的
I believe you are innocent
黄长官，这一次你一定要帮我
Mr.Huang, you must help me on this
老鬼德这一件事，除了我知道之外
Who else knows the old Te case
还有什么人知道？
besides me?
泰利
Terry
你明知道泰利这个人这么冲动
You know Terry is impulsive
你不单只害死了他，还把你自己也害了
Now you've ruined him and yourself
现在首先要做的就是帮你洗脱嫌疑
The first thing is to prove your innocence
你不是说有一盒录影带拷贝吗？带我去拿
Take me to get the copy of cassette you mentioned
你不相信我？
Don't you trust me?
信有
Shun-yu
我昨天录的那一盒带子你有没有看到？
Have you seen the cassette I taped yesterday?
有，除了德叔之外还有...
Yes. Besides Te, there's...
还有什么？你快说
Go on! Speak up!
我不知道，我什么都不知道
I don't know, I don't know anything
究竟知不知道？
Do you know or not?
我什么都不知道
I know nothing
那一盒带子对阿有很重要
The cassette is very important to Yu
知道在什么地方就马上拿出来
Bring it if you know where it is
你不用找了，没有
There's no such a cassette
一定有的，我昨晚在这一部机过带子的
There must be. I ran it on this VTR recorder last night
你想想有没有拿过出来
Have you ever taken it away?
没有，我碰也没有碰过
NO, I didn't even touch it
你刚才又说有？
Just now you said got it
没有那盒带子
Without it
我用水也洗不清要坐一辈子牢
I can't clear myself. I'll be in jail
究竟你知不知道
Do you know it or don't you?
我知道了...
I know...
知道还不快些拿出来
Now get it
你也不想阿有有事的
You don't want Yu to get into trouble
我答应你，我洗脱嫌疑之后就不当警察
I promise. I'll quit once I'm cleared
我好怕
I'm so scared!
你怕什么？找到这一盒带子我就没事了
Why? It's okay if you find the cassette
阿有，好了，我们该走了
Well, Yu, we must leave
爱美不会有事，我会派人看着她
Amy's going to be alright, I'll have someone watch her
我是米高
I'm Michael
我现在在干德道干德花园二十六楼五号
now at 5 Conduit Garden 26th floor
有一个女人需要保护，马上派人来
Send someone, a woman needs protection
阿有，我们要赶时间
Yu, we're in a hurry
我先走了
Excuse me
信有，我不要人保护
Shun Yu, I want no protection
没事的，你放心，我很快就回来
I'm alright, I'll return soon
拜拜
Bye-bye!
走吧
Let's go!
请传呼3388
Please call 3388
爱美，有急事，叫她马上打电话来
Amy urgent. Tell her to call my home
黄长官，现在回去警察局，先把我铐上
Mr.Huang, let's return to Hq Handcuff me
也好，省得回去之后让人家看不过眼
Okay, this will save us from unnecessary complaints
多熬一阵子，洗脱嫌疑之后就没事了
Bear with it now and soon you'll clear your's
黄长官，给你添麻烦了
Mr.Huang, sorry for the trouble
应该的
Don't mention it
黄长官，就是这两个洋鬼子跟德叔交易
Mr.Huang, it was these foreigners who deal with Te
快一点掉头，去捉他
Turn around and arrest them!
爱美，什么事？
Amy, what happened?
莎莉，米高是奸，是他幕后主使德叔贩毒
Shirley, Michael masterminded Te's dope-pushing
米高不会这样吧？
He won't do that
是真的
It's true
他刚刚拿了那一盒录影带走，我现在怕
He just took that cassette away, I'm scared
你镇定一点，千万别走开，我现在马上来
Keep calm, don't go away
到时候你再详细告诉我
Tell me in detail
米高是奸的，是他主使德叔贩毒
Michael mastermined Te's dope-pushing
你相信我...
Believe me...
站着
Stop!
进来
Come in!
这么晚来找我，有什么事？
Why are you coming to see me at this hour
心情不好，别喝那么多酒
You're depressed, don't drink so much
近来发生了这么多事，不如去旅行散散心
After so much has happened, go for a pleasure tour
爱美在临死之前跟我通过电话
Amy spoke to me over the phone before her dead
是吗？
Is that so?
她跟你说过什么话
What did she say to you?
阿有被控藏毒是无辜的
Yu is innocent of drug possession
贩毒的那一个是德叔，幕后有一个大人物
A big shot is behind Te's drug-trafficking
哪是谁？
Who?
你应该比我更清楚
You should know better
是的，我也接到爱美的电话
Yes, I got Amy's phone too
说你跟阿有串谋贩毒
You did drug-trafficking with Yu
我到现在才看清楚你的真面目
Now I really understand you
你到底是不是人？
Are you a human being?
做了那么多事，现在还想嫁祸给我
After all these, and you want to make me the scapegoat
我也可以说你想嫁祸给我
I can say it is you who want to make me the scapegoat
以我今天在警队的声誉，地位和成就
Yes, with my name and position in the police force
我讲的话一定有人相信
my words will convince everyone
现在我告诉你，我米高黄贩毒
Now listen, I Michael Huang am a drug-trafficking
你凭什么指控我？
What have got anything to accuse me of it
我有德叔贩毒录影带的拷贝
I've a copy of Te's drug-trafficking tape
我也有一个拷贝，他犯罪根本跟我没关系
I've a copy too. His crime is not linked with me
我可以指控你
I can testify against you
指控我
Testify against me?
那一盒录影带在全世界发行都没有问题
That tape even if released to the world won't serve any purpose
因为指控我的人只有德叔一个
because only Te can testify against me
云逊，是，我是米高
Vincent, yes, I'm Michael
马上替我把德叔干掉
Finish off Te right away
货我会亲自交给你
I'll hand the stuff over to you in person
我们一直相处得很开心，因为你听我指使
We've been getting on well because you're obedient
不过，很可惜...
But, unfortunately...
请叫冯先生听电话
Mr.Feng, telephone
是，我是
Yes, speaking
加拿大长途电话接通了
The long distance call from Canada is connect
谢谢
Thank you
孩子
Darling
爸爸
Daddy
是
Yes
什么事
What is it?
我明天大清早七点就坐飞机到加拿大去
I'll fly to Canada at 7 tomorrow morning
什么
What?
警察部说我身体不好，批准我提早退休
The Hq has approved my early retirement for health reasons
我寄给你的钱收到了没有？
Have you received my remittance?
不许动
Don't move
老鬼德...
OId Te...
别乱来
No monkey business!
你去死吧
Hell with you!
你妈的，我打死你这个家伙...
Damn, I'll kill you...
打...
Kill...
走
Let's go
你查清楚了吗？
Have you found out everything?
这一封辞职信里面已经解释得很清楚
This resignation letter has explained everything
对于我这次这么晚
I'm extremely sorry
才发现我的手下监守自盗
I didn't discover my subordinate's misbehavour...
我觉得很抱歉
till now
我愿意接受纪律处分，并且接受调查
I ready for disciplinary action and investify
不过我有个要求
But I've a request
我希望亲手捉住这一班人
I wish I could arrest these men myself
在我离职前，希望韦长官多给我一个机会
I hope Mr.Wei will give me this chance before I leave
好，你去做吧
Good, go ahead
谢谢长官
Thank you, sir
各位，我们有足够证据
Ladies and gentleman, we've ample evidence against
证明何雪玲督察、冯建德警长
Insp Ho., Serg Feng
方信有探员，涉嫌贩毒，令大家蒙上污点
and detective Fan for drug-trafficking
我实在难辞其咎
I personally can't shirk the responsible for this disgrace
现在他们畏罪潜逃，并且藏有枪械
They're now fugitives with arms
我们一定要将他们缉捕归案
We must bring them to book
希望各位暂时放下私人的感情
Please put personal feelings aside
如果逮捕的时候遇到反抗，格杀勿论
Shoot anyone on sight who tries to resist
死三八
Bitch!
你要我做的事我已经做，你还未把货给我
I've already done what you want. What about the stuff?
先让我把那个三八干掉
Let me finish off that bitch
不可以，这个三八由我替你搞定
No, I'll fix her for you
今天晚上如果我拿不到货就要你的命
I'll take your life if I can't get the cargo tonight
来吧
Come on
3388，是
3388, yes
告诉他方信有和德叔
Fan and Te have got
在积臣道找到了米高黄贩毒资料
Michael's drug trafficking proof in Jackson Road
叫她尽快来，是，谢谢
Tell her to come at once. Yes, thank you
所有货全在车子后面
All the cargo is in the car
你耍我，妈的
Making fun of me? Damn you
米高黄
Michael Huang
你妈的，一枪打死你便宜了你
Damn killing you with I shot is too good for you
我要你变成瘸子，坐一辈子牢
I want you to be a limply in jail all your life
你是通缉犯，你凭什么拉我
You're wanted. What have you got to arrest
凭我
My will power
我宁愿坐牢也要指证你这个大奸狗
Even by going to jail I must testify against you double dealer
出来
Come out!
出来，奸狗
Come out double-crosser
随机应变，我的枪还在你那里
Be flexible my gun's still with you
滚出来
Get out!
去你妈的...死奸狗...打死你
Damn you double-crosser I'll kill you
我帮你赚了这么多钱，你找人来想干掉我
I made much money for you and you got men to kill me?
我打死你这个奸狗
I'll kill you double crosser!
去死吧
Go to hell!
要你的命
I must take your life
你死了就没有人可以指证我
None can testify against me when you're dead
哪就同归于尽好了
Let's perish together
孬种，奸狗，我撞死你
Scum, traitor, I'll kill you!
去死...
Go to hell!
我是扫毒组总督察米高黄
I'm Anti Hareotics Insp.Huang
他是被通缉的毒犯，拘捕他
He's wanted, arrest him
你才是毒犯
You're a drug trafficker!
你说谎
You lie!
不许动，有什么事回警察局再说
Don't move let's talk it over in the headquarter
米高
Michael
韦长官...
Mr. Wei...
不用说了
No need to talk now
现在有充分证据证明你贩毒，我要拘捕你
We now have ample evidence for your drug trafficking you're under arrest
别过来，不然我打死她
Keep away, or I'll kill her
走
Run
米高，你没有机会走了，投降吧
Michael, you've no chance give up
我手上有她，还有机会
With her in my hands, I do
我不会放过任何机会
and I won't give up
想不到我们又在一起了
So we meet again
把车子开过来
Drive the car over
把车子开过去
Drive the car over away
是，长官
Yes sir
先不要走，委屈你们了
Hold it. Thank you
没有你两位我破不了这一宗案子
Without your help I would have cracked this case
至于你们所受的委屈我会尽力补偿
I'll make good the grievances you've suffered